Breadcrumb
----------

1. [Home](https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/)
2. [Donate](https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/donate)
3. Donor Privacy Policy

Choose a language:

Language EnglishArabic | عربىChinese | 中文Korean | 한국어Portuguese | PortuguêsSpanish | Español

Donor Privacy Policy
====================

The purpose of the [Crohn's & Colitis Foundation](https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/about/) website is to provide information about the Foundation and inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) to people living with [Crohn's disease](https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/what-are-crohns-and-colitis/what-is-crohns-disease/) and [ulcerative colitis](https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/what-are-crohns-and-colitis/what-is-ulcerative-colitis/), as well as to their families and friends, healthcare professionals, and the general public.

What information do we collect and how do we use it?
----------------------------------------------------

You may browse our website without identifying yourself or providing any personally identifiable information. When you interact with us through your computer, however, we do record certain non-identifying site-usage data, such as your number of visits to our website pages. 

If you elect to donate, register for an event, or sign up for any of our publications, you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, address, city, state, zip, phone number, and email address. 

We may use this information to communicate with you by email or postal mail from time to time. The Foundation keeps all names, addresses, and all other personal information supplied by participants of our website strictly confidential. Please keep in mind, however, that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, such as on message boards, through email, or in chat areas, that information may be collected and used by others. 

Some parts of our website may also use "cookies," which are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer through your web browser. You may configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. However if cookies are rejected, some pages on our website may not function properly.

**Please note: Children under the age of 13 should receive parental consent prior to disclosing any personal information.**

Do we share your information?
-----------------------------

For disclosure of demographic information (e.g., rental or exchange of donor lists with other organizations), the Foundation as a minimum will use the "opt-out" approach. An "opt-out" is obtained when the Foundation gives individuals an opportunity to decline or "opt-out" of disclosures to third parties. If an individual does not opt out, permission is deemed granted.

What security do we provide to protect your personal information?
-----------------------------------------------------------------

The Foundation uses multiple electronic and administrative safeguards to protect your information from unauthorized access, such as firewall technologies and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) security, which is described below. Access to your account information is protected via system passwords which are changed periodically. Despite use of these safeguards, we cannot guarantee and do not represent that your information will always be secure from unauthorized access.

Do we provide a secure environment for online transactions?
-----------------------------------------------------------

All credit card information collected through online transactions are processed with SSL security, an established protocol for transmitting information via the Internet which uses server authentication and data encryption to ensure that your data is safe, secure, and available only to authorized staff members of the Foundation.

How can you contact us to review or correct your personal information?
----------------------------------------------------------------------

You may view or edit your personal profile by [logging in](http://online.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/site/UserLogin?NEXTURL=ConsProfileUser) to our website at [www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org,](https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/) where you can also view a history of your online transactions or subscribe to our e-newsletter. In addition, you may also email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or call us at 1-800-932-2423 to review your personal information.

Disclaimer on Information Provided on the Crohn's & Colitis Foundation Website
------------------------------------------------------------------------------

All articles and messages that appear in our website, including notes from physicians and other Foundation-designated participants, are provided for general information purposes only. They do not represent individual medical advice, counsel concerning individual treatments or medical care, referrals to healthcare professionals, or any other recommendations. You should not rely on any information on these pages to replace consultations with your doctor and other qualified healthcare professionals regarding your individual health needs. Statements or opinions expressed by physicians and other independent authors reflect the views of each such individual and do not necessarily reflect the views or any official policy of the Crohn's & Colitis Foundation. 

The Foundation makes every effort to provide accurate and up-to-date information. However, the Foundation expressly disclaims all responsibility and liability arising from your use of or reliance on this website or for the information contained herein as a reference source, and for any advice or other guidance or information provided by any health care provider contributing to this site. 

Except where otherwise noted, all information on the Foundation website, including its design and organization, is copyrighted by the Crohn's & Colitis Foundation Inc. This material is for personal use only. Permission to otherwise reprint or electronically reproduce any document in whole or in part is expressly prohibited, unless prior written consent is obtained from the Foundation.  

The Crohn's & Colitis Foundation's website also contains information copyrighted and owned by entities and individuals other than the Foundation. This information is for personal use only. Permission to otherwise reprint or electronically reproduce any document in whole or in part is expressly prohibited, unless prior written consent is obtained from the owner.  

The Foundation's website also contains third party information. Whenever possible, such information is marked with the name of the source and does not necessarily represent the opinion of the Foundation. We do not take any responsibility whatsoever for such third party information. 

The Foundation's website also contains links to other Internet sites. The Foundation does not necessarily endorse the views expressed in the Internet sites to which it provides links, nor is the organization responsible for the information they contain. The content of these linked sites are the sole responsibility of such sites and their contributing authors. The Foundation does not intend links to other sites to be referrals or endorsements of the linked entities, but rather provides such links for convenience only.

* Donate

Browser not supported
---------------------

Your Internet Explorer is outdated. For optimal security settings and a better experience on our site, try switching to one of these options:

**Google Chrome**

**Firefox**

**Safari** (macOS 10.8+ only)

Ok! I'm aware that I'm using an older browser.

RESEARCH

* About IBD Plexus
